

CONTACT

1 678-826-7321

joshua@informandinspire.llc

Orlando, Florida

joshuadesir.life

SKILLS

- Logo Design
- Brand Strategy
- · Layout Design
- · Social Media Marketing
- Adobe Illustrator
- · Adobe Photoshop
- Inkscape
- Project Management
- Strong Communication

EDUCATION

NORTH AMERICAN TECHNICIAN EXCELLENCE CERTIFICATION

2021

HVAC AND ELECTRCIAL CERTIFICATION

Southern Technical College 2019-2020

STUDIES IN ARCHITECTURE Valencia College 2018-2019

JOSHUA DESIR

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

PROFILE

I am a skilled graphic designer and with 1.5 years of experience of creating brand identities and print designs/marketing. I use design theory and principles to push creative boundaries in a project and inspire creative solutions. I love developing concepts with motivated people and have effective visual and analytical skills.

EXPERIENCE

HEAD DESIGNER AND COFOUNDER

Désirable Solutions

2021 - Present

- · Designing brand identities for small businesses
- · Coordinating projects with web developers
- · Consulting clients on brand strategy
- · Designing graphics for marketing and information

SOLAR ENERGY TECHNICIAN

Vision Solar LLC

Jan 2022 - Jul 2022

- Installed and troubleshooted solar energy systems for residential properties
- Transported all equipment for jobsites
- Managed project inventory

HVAC TECHNAICIAN

Lennox NAS

2020 - 2021

- Repaired and maintained commercial air conditioners for a variety of businesses
- Worked on team installation projects with tradesmen from outside fields
- Documented clear and detailed diagnostics on HVAC systems